("Love Theme From MST3K")
♪ In the not too distant future
♪ Somewhere in time and space
♪ Mike Nelson and his robot pals
♪ Are caught in an endless chase
♪ Pursued by a woman
whose name is Pearl
♪ An evil gal who
wants to rule the world
♪ She threw a few
things in her purse
♪ And in her rocket
ship she hunts him
♪ All across the universe
♪ I'll get you
♪ I'll send him cheesy movies
♪ The worst I can find
♪ He'll have to sit
and watch them all
♪ And I'll monitor his mind
♪ Now keep in mind
Mike can't control
♪ Where the movies begin or end
♪ He'll try to keep his sanity
♪ With the help of
his robot friends
♪ Robot roll call
♪ Cambot, you're on
♪ Gypsy, oh my stars
♪ Tom Servo, check me out
♪ Crow, I'm different
♪ If you're wondering
how he eats and breathes
♪ And other science facts
♪ Just repeat to yourself,
"It's just a show
♪ "I should really just relax"
♪ For Mystery
Science Theater 3000
(doors slam)
- Hi everyone, Mike Nelson here,
welcome to the Satellite--
- Are you ready
for some spirit?
- Huh?
- Alright, alright, alright,
don't chu wanna hear it?
The Satellite of Love
has got oodles of spirit,
yay!
- Okay?
- Gimme an S!
- No.
- Gimme an A!
- Hmm, no.
- Gimme, gimme a T!
- Nuh-uh.
- Well come on, you
gotta give me something.
- Well technically
we don't really.
- Oh c'mon, just
gimme the other T.
- Well what do we get out of it?
- Spirit?
(Mike and Crow mumble)
- Okay, we can give
you an M, an R,
a small X, and one L.
- So MRxL then, woo!
The Satellite of Love
has got MRxL, MRxL, MRxL!
Have you got as much MRxL as us?
I don't think so--
- We'll be right back.
- We got the MRxL--
- MRxL.
- And you got none.
(bright synth music)
- MRxL, uh-huh, MRxL,
MRxL, MRxL, MRxL!
Woo, okay, now throw
me up Mike, MRxL!
(metal crunches)
- Oh, Earl of Pearl is calling.
- [Tom] MRxL?
- Hey Smellson,
feeling my oats today.
Spridel, Chim-Chim, and I
ran right into a
school of Sunnies,
they were all over our jerk bait
like ugly on ape.
- Hey!
- Hey, shut your cake hole,
it's just an expression.
All in all, a pretty nice trip.
We used Brainiac here
as a fish locator
and then he harvested
some wild mushrooms
with his mind, we sat by
a crystal blue stream,
having mind-fried rainbow trout,
it was heaven!
- I got bit by a rattlesnake
in a very embarrassing place,
had to suck the poison
out myself (laughs).
- I'll never eat again.
- And I got stung by a scorpion,
found the mother
load of dear ticks,
sat in some sand burrs,
say got mauled by a bear,
he buried me so he
could eat me later,
and I had to dig my way out.
- Whose story is this?
Anyway, we found some
beautiful wildflowers
and some of these
weird-ass zucchini things,
y'know you should go camping.
Oh that's right, you can't.
(all laugh)
- Well no, but there's
plenty of other stuff--
- Oh yes you can Mike,
you just have to
know how to portage.
You see, with as
few good calm rivers
and streams as there are
on the Satellite of Love,
well one good canoer
must know how to portage.
(canoe slams)
Op, sorry guys, I'm portaging,
but what is portaging really?
(canoe slams)
I mean Webster's
Dictionary defines it
as, "Portage, to
portage or pour-taj,
but what does it mean
for us really, guys?
Guys?
- You wanna watch the, ow!
(canoe slams)
- Portage (laughs).
- Well isn't that
pleasant and quality.
- Yes'em thank you.
- Yes, quality has been inserted
into every sector of our day,
and we wish to
share it with you.
- Please accept these lovely
and decent throw pillows.
- I thought you said
they were zucchini,
now they're throw pillows?
- Yeah, which is it?
- Zucchini.
- Throw pillow.
(both speak at once)
- So they're throw pillows.
- Zucchini.
- They're throw pillows.
Please enjoy their fine quality
and your movie, which is both
called Giant Spider Invasion
and is quite quality.
- Guys I don't know,
I don't think we should accept
these zucchini pillow things.
- Oh don't be so
suspicious Mike,
hey send them babies
up, we'll use them
in the rumpus room (laughs).
You see, they're
perfectly normal
overgrown pod-like
vegetation Mike,
you Nervous Nelly you!
- I think we should
send them back.
(buzzer blares)
Oh, we got Movie Sign!
- [Tom] Hey it's in color!
- [Crow] Color.
Hey it's a Giant Spider
Invasion of savings at Menard's!
- [Tom] Oh this is when
all the spider singers
came over from Great Britain.
♪ Steve Brodie just
closes his eyes again
- [Mike] Wow, staring
Alan D'Oh Hale!
- [Tom] Special but
unknown guest star.
- [Mike] Now how can you
have a guest star in a movie?
Yeah this is an orchestral piece
called The People's Court Suite.
- [Crow] Ah, of the
Beer Barrel Pokras.
♪ Gilett, the best a man can get
- [Mike] It was
executive produced,
at least there's that.
- [Crow] I can see
the Giant Spider
moving slowly towards
us, down and down.
- [Tom] Ah Bill Rebane,
one of the best directors
ever to come out of
North Central Wisconsin.
- [Crow] I hope earth
has it's diaphragm on.
♪ I shot the Sheriff's Office
♪ But I did not shoot
the Deputy's Office
- [Mike] Seamless phone
cups provide support.
- Jeff!
- Hi little buddy!
(audience shouts)
What's happening?
- Oh not much, I
thought I'd stop by,
see if you had a
scoop for the paper.
- [Tom] And show
you my new shirt!
- Pretty quiet
around here Davey.
(Tom hums)
- Well I guess there's nothing
going on in this
neck of the woods
except the revival over
at Gleason Town hall.
- [Mike] It lists George.
- You going?
- No, are you?
- No, I got me a
date with Terry!
- Surprised that Dan Kester
lets you anywhere near her!
- He's her brother-in-law,
not her father.
- Yeah, well don't get
on the wrong side
of him, young fella.
He's a strange man and he's
working up a big head of steam.
- [Ev] Dan?
- [Tom] Jan?
- Where the hell are you going?
- Into town.
- What the hell for?
- [Tom] Promise keepers.
- I'm going to a revival.
- Well you need it!.
- [Crow] There's my rat!
- Sometimes the only way
I know you're still
alive is when I hear you
flush the toilet.
- [Tom] Yeah, like
they have a toilet.
♪ Love, soft as an easy chair
- Hallelujah!
- [Crow] Zig Ziglar.
- The joy that you're
feeling right now
is just the beginning.
- [Tom] It better be.
- Our revival is
gonna grow and grow
for the next four days.
Days that are gonna
change your life.
- [Crow] Meanwhile
a glowing splint
from a high school vo-tech
class speeds towards Earth.
- [Dave] Hi, Terry ready yet?
- No, not quite.
You wanna little drink?
- Oh no thanks, Mrs. Kester,
I'll just wait right here.
- [Tom] Casual day at Hazelton.
- Okay, Ev.
- Sure you don't want one?
- [Dave] No, I'm sure.
- Terry might be
quite a while yet.
- You know you are Terry don't
look much alike for sisters,
but I gotta say that good
looks run in your family.
- Well, thank you Dave.
You know it's too bad
that there's this little
age difference between us.
- [Tom] She's drinking
fermented Yoo-Hoo.
- If you were five years older,
I'd jump you.
- [Mike] Well I got
cables in the car, ma'am.
- You look great,
doesn't she Mrs. Kester?
- [Tom] I'm ready for
some muskrat loving.
- Yes.
- C'mon Terry.
- [Tom] Bye little slutster.
- [Mike] Saved a lot
buying the old Gein place.
- [Crow] I suppose I should move
grandma's body out
of the den now.
(spooky synth music)
- Fore!
(phones rings)
- D'oh!
- Hello, Sherriff's Office?
- [Crow] Professor
made a toaster
out of coconuts, why?
- I see, uh-huh.
Disturbing the peace?
- [Tom] We could do that.
- Yes ma'am, that's
an arrestable offense.
- [Mike] Repeat what you say
to provide exposition?
- No, the law does not
apply to preaching.
- Hellfire and brimstone,
that is what is
in store for you.
- [Mike] Dennis
Rodman, listening?
- It's right here,
Psalms 11, verse six,
"Upon the wicked He shall
reign fire and brimstone."
(spooky synth music)
- Oh, and spiders!
- [Crow] I need one
room in Las Vegas
and a lot of liquor, please.
- Dutch, this is it.
Listen there's not
a drop of booze
left in this house, I
just can't stand it,
I'm really desperate.
Would you bring me something?
- [Crow] This is not the
purpose of 911, ma'am.
- [Mike] A pony keg
should tide me over.
- Oh thanks, Dutch.
Listen, listen, you'll
find me very appreciative
when you get here.
- [Mike] I saved you
half a can of Pringles.
- Bye-bye.
- [Crow] Dad's so understanding.
- [Tom] How about this (beeps),
can you hear this (beeps)?
- Well, here we are.
(funky jazz music)
- [Crow] The Joe
Don Baker Museum.
- You've gotta be kidding?
- You said, "Park."
- [Mike] Crank up
the Molly Hatchet
and go to down.
- [Crow] "I like
you Donnie, like!"
- Can you come again
tomorrow night?
- Well I certainly hope so.
- The revival will
be still here.
- Gimme that old time religion.
(laughs) I can hardly wait
to get saved again
tomorrow night!
- Oh Dan, wait.
- [Crow] I forgot to
validate your parking.
- You forgot your back brace!
(audience groans)
- [Mike] Oh my.
Oh, he's pink.
- [Tom] I don't know how,
but I just became sterile.
- [Crow] Go spiders, go spiders,
go, go, spiders.
- Bright, noble star fall
from Heaven to the Earth,
and there erode a
smoke out of the pit,
and the smoke from
a great furnace.
- [Mike] Then add
the ribs and cook.
- And out of the smoke,
there came locusts
upon the Earth
and unto them was given power.
- [Tom] Can I just
get my Tupperware?
- [Crow] Pull up Leica, pull up!
♪ I love tick-infested hounds
♪ Slaughtering a deer, and beer
- [Tom] Ah, Brett Favre at home.
- [Mike] Now they're
poor only in money,
and spirit, and dignity, and
moral fiber, and hygiene.
- [Crow] Hi Hud.
- How was it?
- [Crow] How was your
day at the whore?
- Great.
- Ribbitt.
- Well what did the
preacher talk about?
- Sin?
♪ Like a rock
- [Ev] What did he
have to say about it?
- He was against it.
- Listen damn it--
- [Tom] Can we get the
boom mic a little closer?
- [Mike] The movie that
takes the bold step
of not including the audience.
- Look at that!
(explosion)
- [Tom] Laserium, with
music by Pink Floyd.
- [Crow] Hooterville
was decimated
by SCUD missiles that day.
- What the hell was that?
- Wind.
Jeez, would you
listen to that wind?
- [Mike] Meanwhile, a
woman needs a light wrap.
- Light's are dead.
- What's wrong?
- [Tom] You could rub
their (mumbles) together
and create static to keep
warm if they're cold.
- Car won't start either.
- [Mike] And my
skin's getting waxy.
- [Terry] Oh great.
- Wait here Terry.
- [Crow] I'll turn
off the wind machine.
- [Tom] It's the new 1971 Car!
- [Mike] Well the
air filter's fine.
- C'mon!
- [Crow] I figure
we can have sex
'til this blows over.
- [Tom] Albert Camus!
Safe!
- [Mike] Moses, move the bike!
- [Tom] Well I hope
that bomb didn't land
on our pile of tires and
our busted refrigerator
in the yard, and the rusted
chassis of our '68 Impala.
- What the Hell was that?
- [Mike] It's befuddling
my dumb cracker mind!
- [Crow] Steve Prefontaine!
- [Tom] Satan's out running.
- [Mike] Normalfoot!
It's like Bigfoot.
♪ Like a rock
- [Mike] Okay (laughs).
I think that's a little much.
- [Dan] No fire, no smoke,
no smell, no sound, nothing.
- You saw it too!
It wasn't just me, you saw it!
There must be
something out there.
- [Tom] Of course we
are dumb Cheeseheads.
- Well whatever it is,
it can keep till morning.
- [Mike] I'll leave
the light on for ya.
- [Ev] You mean to
say that all Hell
just busted loose in our field,
and you're going on into bed?
- [Dan] I'm tired!
- [Crow] And
repulsive and stupid.
- [Ev] You're always tired.
- Well that revival
really took it out of me.
Now if you want to,
you can stay out here
all night looking at nothing.
- [Tom] This isn't a very
good remake of Sabrina.
- [Crow] Packers fans,
the horrible truth.
♪ Lush
♪ It's the good life
(bright synth music)
(alarm blares)
- [Crow] America Online
tries to keep up.
- [Tom] Red phones are
hot in Paris this spring.
(phone rings)
- [Mike] Yeah, he's got a copy
of Varmit Master
hidden inside that.
- Hello?
Sheriff's Office?
- [Crow] Oh don't act
with your tongue out.
- I see.
- [Tom] I should
button my shirt.
- You say your radio won't work?
Well all I can tell you
is call Joe's Radio Shop.
He opens 9:00 am sharp.
- [Mike] You say your space age
missile defense
system won't work?
- And your car won't start?
- [Crow] Then you
might be a redneck.
- Well all I can tell you
is call Ernie's Auto
repair, he opens at eight!
- [Mike] Maybe he's Amish
and doesn't believe in buttons.
- No ma'am, I don't
have the number.
- [Tom] Take your time, movie.
- All I can tell you is
use the Yellow Pages.
Let your fingers do the walking.
- [Crow] Not a joke, but
an incredible simulation.
- That's funny, I wonder
why she hung up on me?
- [Mike] Maybe your bodily funk
travels over the phone lines?
- [Tom] Actually filmed
inside the thumb hole
of a bowling ball.
- [Crow] Film Extra Noir.
- [Mike] Hello, Movie?
C'mon Movie, c'mere boy!
(Tom whsitles)
- [Dan] Don't move
or I'll shoot!
- [Tom] Don't turn on the light!
(audience groans)
- That scared the
death out of me.
- [Mike] He's lactating!
- Put the gun away.
- What the hell are you doing
sneaking in here at this hour?
- [Mike] What a handsome man.
- [Tom] Young Bill and Hillary
struggle to make it.
- I warned you,
that little Perkins
snot is rotten.
- [Crow] Wanna piece of milk?
- It wasn't Dave's fault,
his car broke down.
- [Mike] Would you
call this food?
- You fell for that!
- [Tom] Oh McGoo,
you've done it again!
- Whiksers on it
when I was a kid!
- It really did break down!
- Well, where?
- The junk yard.
- [Crow] Must be like a
homecoming for you, eh Mike?
- That's exactly where
a horny little punk
like that would
park, in a junk yard.
- [Tom] Our proud
Viking heritage.
- I hate to burst your bubble,
but it was my idea.
- I wanna put you over my knee,
pull down your britches, and
spank the Hell out of ya!
- (screams) I always wondered
why you used to
spanked me so much,
so you can get your jollies!
- [Mike] And the movie
ramps up the repulsion.
- [Crow] This movie
hates us, doesn't it?
- [Tom] Well I better finish
my silverfish encroute.
- Man can't even have any
peace in his own house.
- [Mike] Well Section
Eight owns the house, but.
- [Crow] A showered
person, thank God.
- [Tom] Guys, it's Della Street!
- [Mike] It's the hotline
to Paul's Operatives.
- [Crow] Mr. Kester, all
your tests are positive.
- Yes, this is Dr. Langer from
Montclair Observatory again,
Iúve got a gamma ray shower
and the barometerús
dropped an inch
in the last 20 minutes.
- [Crow] Should I
wear shorts or slacks?
- That's unprecedented,
right right.
And none of the other phenomenon
I'm recording correlate
with any previously observed
data in this area.
- [Mike] So I thought we
should cut to Cape Canaveral.
- [Tom] The story of
regional planning,
careful zoning regulation,
rational development controls.
- [Crow] The philodendron story!
- [Mike] Polish toilet
paper dispenser,
that's great, I
gotta put that up.
- Did I ever tell
you you're gorgeous?
- Not recently.
(audience laughs)
- Oh how many times
do I have to tell you?
You talk to plants
to make them grow.
- Talk to plants?
- Not you Vance,
you haven't fallen for
that metaphysical nonsense.
- Well my MO says that
I am half metaphysics
and half astrophysics.
- [Crow] NASA's double wide.
- Now what made you take
the long walk down the hall?
- More freaky stuff
from Northern Wisconsin.
- Freaky?
- Well drunk.
- We just got a report in
that's right out of Ripley.
- And what's the source?
- Montclair Observatory
and Dr. J Langer.
- Langer?
- I like the movie's paneling.
- "We have a heavy
gamma ray shower,
"an incredibly fast drop
in barometric pressure,
"an aurora with no sun activity,
"and an amazingly potent,
"unknown ground-level
X-ray source nearby."
- [Crow] Who put those
pencils up there?
(soft piano music)
- Paul.
- [Mike] Oh Paul.
- Didn't we receive
a sack report
on a fouled up B-52?
- Yeah.
- [Tom] Would I look
good in short-shorts?
- Was it in the same quadrant?
- [Crow] I'm too
embarrassed to answer, sir.
- Oh, you're right.
It was--
- [Mike] Ignore the blood here.
- [Paul] Right here,
then it disappeared
off the radar scope.
- Any report of a
crash in that area.
- No.
- [Mike] Can I go?
- What's the closest town?
- Horton.
- [Crow] Where they hear Who's!
- You better pack your suitcase.
- I'm wearing it old buddy.
- [Mike] Aw, you're
not wearing it,
you old son of a (laughs)!
- Good, 'cause I've already
arranged your transportation.
- Grumpy old losers!
- Thanks a lot.
♪ She ran calling wildfire
- [Mike] What a remarkable pig.
(phone rings)
- [Crow] Cut, print,
beautiful, we got it.
- [Tom] I heard this actor
got this in one take.
- [Mike] Ah, the bright promise
of a disgusting new character.
- [Crow] His arm looks like
it's carved out of lard.
- [Tom] It's Mean
Gene Oakerland!
- [Mike] Right in the
middle of my heart attack.
- [Crow] Concierge?
- Seven o'clock already?
- No, it's 6:02.
- Well what?
Oh, not you again.
- [Tom] Why don't
you just come over?
- Okay, what's up Ryder?
- Well we just got a
report from an orphorator
in the middle of--
- What's an orphorator?
- Oh, that's beautiful, did
you check on the car ferries
on Lake Michigan?
- No no Vance, this is serious,
A couple of seamen
aboard the ship
saw a plane crash,
and it just might be ours.
- Any signs of survivors?
- We don't know.
- Okay Dad, keep
in touch, oh Ryder.
- [Mike] There went my heart.
- What time am I supposed
to meet this (snaps)--
- [Tom] Your waddle's
dripping sir.
- Langer at the Observatory.
- You're expected
at nine, sharp.
- Nine I can make, but if
I don't get some shut eye,
I'm gonna be very sharp, bye.
- Goodbye.
- [Crow] They met
discussing hair oil,
they've been friends ever since.
- [Mike] My waddle
needs five more minutes.
- [Tom] 123, 124, 125.
- [Ev] Great pen is
separate already.
- So.
- So when the Hell
are you gonna get
off your big, fat ass
and go see what happened
in our pasture last night?
- [Crow] That deserves
a thoughtful answer.
- Let me eat my
breakfast in peace.
I gotta keep up my strength.
- [Mike] Tearing
food stamps is hard.
- What for?
- [Crow] Ah, the Walmart family.
- [Jenny] The more
usual kinds of stars
are what we astronomers call
the main sequence stars,
and they run the gammit
from the Blue Giants
to the Red Dwarves.
- [Tom] Like Linda Hunt.
- And then the more
fascinating stars,
we call abnormal stars.
- [Crow] Like Linda Hunt.
- And then we have
the White Dwarves.
- [Mike] Like Linda Hunt.
- And they have a radius
of less than 1/100 of our sun,
and a density that so great
that even a teaspoon
of this matter--
- [Tom] Tee-hee, tee-hee.
- [Langer] Would weigh tons,
and it could only be
lifted by a giant crane.
- [Crow] I will
grow into my beauty.
- Then there are the Quasars,
Neutron stars, and Black Holes,
or Collapsed Stars.
- [Crow] Like Robert Downey.
- [Langer] Now let me show you
my conception of the
creation of this universe.
- [All] No!
- Out of this
primordial fireball,
the galaxies, planets, and stars
of our universe were created.
- [Crow] What about the
black UN helicopters man?
- As you can see, our
sun is but one small star
in a galaxy such as this.
- [Crow] Bra snap, took,
bra snap, bra snap, took.
- Consists of not only the
stars that we've talked about.
- [Crow] Petting,
took, kiss, grope,
bra snap, snooze, spitball.
- And to which they
ultimately return,
but now let's go back
to the Collapsed Stars,
or the Neutron Stars,
Quasars, or Black Holes.
- Oh let's.
- Yeah, let's not.
(multiple people speak at once)
(doors slam)
- Oh hey Gyps, what
happened to the zucchini
throw pillow things that
Mrs. Forrester sent up?
- I put them in a safe place.
- Okay, and where's that?
- A place where you would
meet a horrible demise
before laying your
polluting fingers upon them.
- So you put 'em in
Mike's laundry basket?
(robots laugh)
- And now you should sleep,
I have prepared warm
milk to help you.
- But I'm not tired.
- But all sentient beings,
however inferior, require sleep.
- You okay, Gyps?
- Of course I am,
Mitchel Nelson,
and now you must sleep.
Perhaps a simple
lullaby will aid you?
♪ Close your eyes, go to sleep
♪ Be absorbed by the collective
- That's great Gypsy,
but get over here.
What's wrong with Gypsy?
- What are you talking about?
She's no different that usual.
- Listen.
♪ Fade away, lose your soul
♪ Be replaced by a drone
- Something's taken her over!
- You have one vivid
imagination there, Mike.
- Yeah, kinda paranoid
if you ask me.
- Paranoid?
♪ Let an evil
super consciousness
♪ Swallow you whole
- There, there, you
ever hear her sing
about evil super consciousnesses
swallowing us whole?
- Maybe you have a point, Mike.
- Nah, I've heard her sing
about that stuff lots of times.
- No, that's not her
and whatever it is
wants us to fall asleep,
we have to stay
awake no matter what.
- Are you approaching a state
of relaxing quality sleep yet?
- Just about, we'll
be right with ya.
We'll be right back.
- You see I think we just forgot
her birthday or something.
♪ Give it up
(bright synth music)
- [Tom] That was weird.
Oh man, I'm gonna kill the
guy who invented stairs.
- [Crow] Why can't
colleges in ranch homes?
- [Tom] One heart
attack per landing,
if I can keep it
to that (pants).
- [Mike] Sounds
like a nice place,
wish we could see it.
- [Tom] He's entering through
the kitchen at the Copa.
- [Crow] Obstetrics,
Endocrinology, waddle removal,
here it is.
- [Vance] Hi!
- [Crow] How's everybody doing?
- [Vance] Hello,
I am Dr. JR Vance.
- [Crow] Dr. (slurs).
- I'm so glad
you're here Doctor,
I'm Jenny Langer.
- [Crow] Smoker, coffee drinker.
- Nice to meet you.
I have an appointment
with your father.
- Oh no no, he
past away in 1956.
- Oh I'm so sorry,
then the appointment must
be with your husband.
- [Mike] Go Waddle Man.
- And that's alright.
Then it's probably
with your brother.
- No my brother's an interior
decorator is Oshgosh.
You see Dr. Vance,
I'm afraid your
appointment is with me,
I'm Dr. Jenny Langer.
- [Tom] Humor of the 1840's!
- And we have some very
important business to discuss.
- [Crow] So you've
had a sex change?
- [Mike] She's wearing (mumbles)
if I'm not mistaken.
- [Jenny] Ever been here before?
- No but it's beautiful,
the trees, the green foliage.
- [Tom] It's so banal.
- I'm very fond of plants.
- Oh?
- You know what
we have at NASA?
- [Jenny] No, what?
- Green tile and chrome.
- [Jenny] (laughs) You
don't look the type.
- [Crow] Such a nice day
and they're wasting
it making this movie.
- Well Doctor, do
you wanna clue me in?
- I'd certainly like to.
You see it was after the
lecture last night, Mr. Vance,
that I suddenly discovered
there were many peculiar
things happening.
- [Tom] So you're a woman!
- Yeah like the
gamma ray shower,
the aurora, and the barometer
dropping like Wall Street.
- Exactly, and
that's when I made
those urgent calls to NASA,
frankly speaking
I'm very concerned.
- [Mike] She dresses
like Johnny Carson.
- Well frankly speaking Doctor--
- [Crow] I wanna see that
pantsuit hit the floor.
- This is the United
States government.
- [Tom] Let's go to Mass.
- I'm still measuring
an X-ray shower
from the ground level,
at a magnitude never
before measured on Earth
except a nuclear explosion.
- [Mike] Well I gotta
clean out the prefilter
and then I'll be back, okay?
- It could be an aborted strike
from a unfriendly power.
- Oh come on, you don't think
a missile landed here?
- That's one possibility, yes.
- [Crow] Up yours.
- It could have been
a falling object
like a meteorite, not a missile.
- [Vance] Doctor a meteorite
would have made a
tremendous explosion.
- [Mike] Hey Dad, how do
you like my first web?
- Hello Doctor.
- Anything new?
- Nothing.
- Oh Mary,
this is Mr. Vance from
NASA, Mary Johnson.
- Hello.
- Hello Mary.
- [Crow] I suppose
you're a woman too.
- Doctor, your water's boiling.
- Mary must have forgotten it,
would you like some tea?
- Tea?
(laughs) That's not my brand.
- Here are the reports
from last night.
- [Tom] Shot on location
in Ms. Herberber's bio class.
- [Jenny] Now let's
see what happens today.
- [Crow] Divide
by 10 in minutes!
Add up to three
columns in an hour.
- [Mike] Your order's number
57, please pull ahead.
- [Crow] Oh I see, the
salad wasn't included, huh?
- [Tom] So the one thing they
mic is the adding machine.
Did you beef?
- Look at this.
- Wow.
- Lotta croppies down there.
- The radiation
level is still high.
Whatever landed
hasn't gone away.
- [Tom] Are you as
turned off as I am?
- [Mike] Oof, I'm having
another heart attack.
- Y'know Doctor, I think
I will have that tea.
- [Crow] It's always funny
when you turn down tea,
and then you decide
you want tea.
- [Tom] Greg Norman
at the Master's.
- [Dan] I told you there
was nothing out here.
- [Mike] Shh, the
flowers are listening.
- [Dan] There's nothing.
- [Ev] So why are you
carrying your gun?
- [Dan] Aw, shut up.
♪ There is love
- Since you've been
running the place,
everything's gone wrong.
- [Mike] Woop, plot hole.
(woman screams)
- [Mike] Got milk?
- Now watch this.
- [Crow] I'm gonna
put on a dashiki
and blow your mind.
- See?
♪ What a lucky man he was
- I just don't understand it.
- [Mike] The things I can
do with my spirograph.
- Those radiation levels
are far too lethal.
Anyone anywhere near
the initial impact point
would be in great danger.
- What would be the safest way
to find the exact
point of impact?
- [Crow] Have you do it.
- Maybe we could
use a helicopter.
- No no, that'd
be too dangerous.
Doctor--
- He's got a hatchet wound!
- We have already lost
one airplane crew.
- I didn't know that.
- [Crow] 30 lashes
with a wet noodle.
- Well--
- Well, back to the tea.
- [Crow] There it
is again, boom!
- [Tom] Oh McRib
sandwich with McFlies.
- [Dan] There's another one!
- [Mike] Were we supposed
to be feeding the cattle?
- [Crow] Well Bessie'd
been depressed,
but I didn't think
she'd do this.
- [Tom] C'mon moo, moo damn it!
- [Dan] I can't tell
what kinda critter
coulda done that!
- [Mike] Cow tipping
gone horribly wrong.
- Eight dead cows and a calf.
You realize what this
is gonna cost us?
- It ain't gonna
cost us nothing.
- Nine dead animals ain't
gonna cost us nothing?
- You're so dumb you
wouldn't know rabbit turds
from Rice Crispies.
- [Crow] Snap Crackle Poop.
- I'll butcher up the
meat as I always do
and I'll sell it
to Dutch's Cafe.
- [Tom] Or to Jack in the Box.
- You don't even know
what killed those cows!
There might be something
horrible wrong with the meat.
- Well that's Dutch's
lookout, not mine.
- [Mike] Brought to you
by the Pork Council.
- [Tom] Dutch's Cafe,
on the beltline.
- I've never seen so much
fouled up data in my life.
It's against every
known law of physics.
- [Mike] Except that
one that I don't know.
- Well, we've tried
to brainstorm it.
- [Mike] We've tried
scrubbing it out.
- No, it just won't brainstorm.
- Right.
♪ Take your pantsuit
from your back
- What are we gonna do?
- [Crow] Ghostbusters!
- [Mike] Let's go down to
Dutch's for some meatloaf.
- Doctor, do you have
a Geiger counter?
- Yeah, in the other office.
- Good.
- Well whoopee for you.
- Let's see if your local
sheriff will support us.
- Sheriff Jones (laughs)?
Our Jolly Red Giant?
I know just where
he is, let's go.
- [Crow] Anyway,
Sixth Hour Bio Lab's
about to start,
they need the room.
- You're gonna love him.
You know he believes
in (mumbles) theory.
That the moon came out
of the Pacific Ocean.
- So do I.
- [Mike] Y'know I don't look
at that table that often,
just occasionally, really
it's kind of a periodic table.
- [Crow] I love
summer in Wisconsin,
meat rotting in the fields.
- [Mike] The hills are alive
with the stink of that guy,
his back brace is smelly.
- [Ev] Dutch is gonna
want that much meat.
- [Dan] SO I'll
freeze some of it up
and sell it to him later.
- [Tom] Honey, I
don't feel fresh.
- Hey look at this.
- [Crow] I could
distill it and drink it!
- I've never seen a rock
like that around here.
- [Mike] Y'know this
movie tested well
with sexual predators.
- [Tom] Maybe it's breadfruit!
- [Crow] Honey, let's play
William Burroughs and Joan.
- [Mike] These two have every
Married with Children on tape.
- [Tom] Well maybe we
never planted corn.
- Wow, look at that.
I told you something
landed here last night.
- [Crow] There's a 747
just sitting there!
- [Mike] We've got
giant prairie dogs!
- [Tom] Mork of Ork was
taken to St. Mary's Hospital,
bur pronounced dead on arrival.
- [Dan] I don't know, you
can't tell from the outside.
- [Crow] I better climb in one
and see what it is.
- [Mike] Maybe their
round arrow heads.
- [Tom] I'll juggle my
way back to his heart.
- [Crow] And the Giant
Spider Invasion begins now!
- [Tom] And now, begin.
(bright synth music)
- And good morning to you all!
Hey Helga, you're
looking bright-eyed
and bushy-tailed!
You musta had some kind of a
heavy date last night, huh?
- You better believe it.
- One of the loggers?
- That's my secret.
- [Mike] What a
delightful pig I am.
- Ah Dutch, you've got
that Linberger cheese
smile on your face
again this morning.
Had trouble last night?
- Yeah.
- One of the loggers?
- What does that mean?
- I don't know, I
had trouble myself!
- [Mike] Just random words.
- Seemed like everybody
was calling up
with some cockamamie
little thing.
The car wouldn't start,
the radio wouldn't work,
and the preacher man kept
everybody awake last night!
- When does that
gospel wonga go on?
- I don't know,
but I'll tell ya,
he may work for God,
but he sure hollers
like the Devil (laughs).
- [Crow] Oh Alan!
- [Mike] I gotta go
drain the little buddy,
I'll be right back.
- Breakfast is ready.
- [Tom] Here's
your steak and eggs
with deep-fried butter.
- [Crow] Welcome to Hooters.
- [Mike] Well my
thumb's clean off now.
- No, it's not gonna work,
go get me a hammer.
- [Tom] No wonder
I was constipated.
- [Crow] These are not a
lovely bunch of coconuts.
- [Mike] We're out of gin.
- Not that one, the big one.
- [Tom] Stanley!
- And a chisel.
- [Crow] I don't
care what you use,
just hit the guy!
- [Mike] It's the lead
singer of the Spin Doctors.
- [Crow] Here's
your liver honey,
I packed it nice.
- Get it yourself.
- [Mike] I'm glad
he's not a Moyle.
- [Tom] Honey MIT called.
(monkey grunts)
- [Crow] Man this
floor is disgusting.
- You never were any
good with a tool.
- [Mike] Ah, the Ropers.
- Hey look!
- My toenail finally fell off.
- It split.
- [Crow] Let me see.
- They look like diamonds.
- I don't know.
- Let's get Mikey to try it.
- May not be hard
enough to be a diamond.
- Don't hit it, no no,
diamonds are supposed
to cut glass.
- [Crow] They're supposed to,
but they're too damn lazy.
- [Mike] You see
he remembers that
from his last year of
school in third grade.
- [Tom] Too bad their windows
are made from cellophane
and duct tape.
- [Crow] Aryan Nation rules.
- Look at that!
- [Mike] I made a R!
(Tom hums)
- Oh hi Dr. Langer!
How are you this morning,
won't you join me please?
- [Crow] Round of
bacon, I'm buying.
- This your brother
from Oshgosh?
- No, this is Dr.
Vance from NASA.
- [Vance] Hello sheriff.
- NASA?
National Aeronautics and Space
Administration, that NASA?
- Yes, but it's
NASA, Houston Texas.
- Sheriff, we have
to talk to you
about last night's disturbances.
- Say no more, I'll
get that preacher man
to tone it down tonight.
- No no, I don't mean
that disturbance.
- Oh no?
Pardon me, Doctor.
- [Tom] There's a crumb
I didn't eat there.
- One of our local
spiders (laughs).
- [Crow] So it's stupid
and smells of beer sweat?
- Hey, what's that gizmo?
- [Tom] It's my pacemaker.
- [Vance] It's a Geiger counter.
- A Geiger counter?
Well we don't have any
Geigers around here,
never did in these parts!
- [Mike] Kill him!
- See Dr. Geiger invented this
to count the nuclear--
- Oh Vance, Vance,
I have a feeling the
sheriff's putting you on.
I'm sure he's taken physics.
- Oh I used to take physics,
but now I find that--
- [Crow] Joke coming in!
- Prunes do the
better job for me!
(audience groans)
- We're gonna be rich!
- Whaddya mean we?
- [Tom] You, me and booze!
- This farm is mine.
Everything that's on it is mine.
- [Mike] Every dead cow.
- Nobody ever found diamonds
around here before.
I think they came out
of that weird fireball
thing last night.
(Mike farts)
- I'll take this into cousin
Billy at the rock shop.
- [Tom] Billy!
- He can tell me just
exactly what they're worth.
- But don't you tell cousin
Billy where you found 'em.
That'll be our secret.
- [Tom] Al Vinyl,
honey I love you!
- Don't look at
me like that Dan,
you and me are gonna be rich!
- [Mike] Think of the
toilet you can buy!
- Dan listen, I never meant
any of those nasty things
I used to say to you,
I was just teasing.
- [Crow] I'm gonna
call off the invasion,
this place is just not worth it.
- [Tom] It's them welfare
moms sucking us dry.
- [Dave] Hi Dr. Langer,
morning sheriff.
- Morning.
- Hello dear.
- May I join you?
- Please.
- Thank you.
- This is Dave Perkins,
his father runs a
local newspaper.
- [Crow] He's Mrs. Pynchon.
- Nice to see you.
- Nice to meet you.
- Dr. Vance from NASA.
- NASA huh?
- NASA, Houston.
- [Mike] Where they
have a problem.
- What brings you here?
Anything I can
publish in the paper?
- Well that's classified.
- Well, I'll put it in
the classified section.
- (laughs) Well
that's safe enough,
nobody read your ads anyway!
- [Tom] What a fun sheriff.
- Now Dave, could I speak
to you for a moment.
- [Dave] Sure Dr. Vance.
- [Crow] But no touching.
- [Vance] Excuse
us for a moment.
- [Mike] Now do you recommend
the chicken fried steak
or the walleye cheeks?
- [Crow] Pudding!
- [Mike] Yeah you
can borrow my shirt.
- Is he always that serious?
- He probably has
something to be serious
about this time.
- You know I wonder
if what happened
to Terry and I last
night has something
to do with what
you're talking about.
- What?
- What happened
to you and Terry?
- [Tom] First base, whew!
- By the junk yard,
the lights, they went dead,
the radio wouldn't work
and the engine wouldn't start.
The wind came up and
started, I don't know,
everything just went wrong.
- [Tom] Thoughtful or
hungry, you decide.
- [Mike] Hour three
of the invasion,
we took the refrigerator.
- [Crow] Thanks for
breakfast ma'am,
I'll clean up.
- [Mike] Doctor should
have been more specific
when he told her to
get plenty of fluids.
Honey I need changing again.
- You're hitting the
booze again, huh?
- Leave me alone,
I feel terrible.
This place is full of spiders.
- Yeah, I know.
Little pink ones.
- No no, big, big
black hairy ones,
with furry legs.
- [Crow] No that's me.
- Lay off the booze,
Ev and they'll go away.
- [Mike] Y'know in her defense,
laying off the booze would
mean seeing him sober.
- [Crow] It's true.
(phone rings)
- [Mike] Joey Hasbeen.
- Hello, Sheriff's office?
Oh yes Mrs. Cooper, how are you?
- [Tom] Pancakes,
I'll be right over!
- Missing?
- Well where are you?
Well take a good look around
and that's where you would be.
- Where'd you see him last?
- [Mike] 1953?
- You haven't seen
him since last night?
Well I'd be glad to drive out
and take a look for him,
what color is his motorcycle?
- [Tom] Personally
I've never been able
to start seeing motorcycles.
- C'mon dear, please
stop worrying,
I'm sure he'll turn
up safe and sound.
- [Crow] I'll be there
after my pre-lunch snack.
- Yes, I'll get
in touch with you.
Right, bye.
(bright synth music)
- Boy, how come
you only get tired
when you have to stay awake
to avoid being replaced by an
evil pod creature, huh Servo?
Servo!
- I'm awake Mike,
I can stay awake, I just
need a little shut eye.
- No no no no, don't
pass out on me now,
we have to stay awake
to avoid being replaced
by a pod creature from
Gypsy's evil doppleganger.
- Please Mike, (speaks German).
(Both speak German)
- Round your lips.
- I'll round your lips.
Crow!
- I'm fine, I'm fine,
Mike I have French roast,
Vivaren, diet pills,
Mountain Dew, Jolt,
water Joe, Surge,
chocolate covered
espresso beans, M&M's,
and I'm listening to (mumbles)
and I'm fine Mike,
really I'm fine.
- Alright okay,
just don't explode.
- Okay, Roger.
- I'm gonna check in
on the planet here.
- Hi Nelson, just getting
the last of these ticks off.
- Bobo, is that you?
I mean really you?
- No it's John Shuck
on a bad hair day,
of course it's me, and I'm fine.
But these two (laughs),
they really love
their zucchinis!
In fact, they're packing them up
so that they can deliver
zucchinis to their friends
all over the galaxy!
- Now listen very
carefully Bobo,
those pods grow aliens
that replace your body,
if they're loading
them into the truck,
that means the whole
galaxy could be in danger!
- Oh come now, just
because they load
a bunch of zucchini
throw pillows
onto a truck, doesn't mean
they're trying to
take over the galaxy.
(laughs) Preposterous,
typical of you
with your Beck and your
bra and hand blenders.
Well look, I'll just ask her.
Oh hey Law Giver, now
are those evil pods
and are you trying to
take over the galaxy?
- Yes and yes, excuse me please.
- Well I guess I can see
how you could
misconstrue that Nelson,
but I'm still not convinced.
- What do you mean?
Calm down, look
just do me a favor
and try taking one of
those pods off the truck.
- Alright, I'll humor you.
Let me see if I can grab
one of these babies here.
There we go.
Hmm, I don't remember taking
another one of those with me.
Well now, this is odd,
and she did say she wanted
to take over the galazy.
(Pearl screams)
Nelson I see your point,
you may be onto something!
The universe is in danger,
but don't you worry,
no sirree Bob,
I'm on the job!
I'll stop these two
wretched creatures
and foil their little plan.
(Bobo's speech is
muffled by rope)
- Well again, we're doomed.
- What's that horrible thumping?
- It's my heart.
I think I'm--
- He's gonna blow!
(alarms blare)
- [Crow] Hurry up, hurry
up you guys, please!
- [Mike] The last
(mumbles), wee-hee!
- [Tom] I'm gonna
pre-bury myself
to save time after I die.
- [Crow] He's a
freelance pooper scooper!
- [Mike] They whacked
the Cryptkeeper!
- [Crow] Whatever it is, it's
drizzled with chocolate sauce!
- [Mike] Honey, you up?
- [Tom] George Hamilton
finally over-tans.
- [Crow] Death of
a kabuki actor.
(heart beats)
- [Tom] Does the
coroner need to know?
- [Crow] I'd like
to say a few words,
this guy's dead,
the end, thank you.
- [Mike] Well happy Arbor Day.
- [Crow] What was that
waiter's name in Paris?
Jean Luc!
- [Mike] Hey Gary,
does this strike you
as a really gross
planet we're invading?
- [Crow] Wait, what
am I doing, Jeez!
- You okay?
- I'm coming down, thanks!
- [Mike] What, do they
keep their garbage
in the refrigerator?
- [Tom] An afternoon
with Sandra Loch!
- [Crow] I'm not looking,
repeat not looking
at the contents of the blender.
- [Mike] These people
are really the backbone
of your casino-based economy.
- What's the matter with you?
- [Crow] Just caught
a glimpse of myself
in the hallway mirror.
- [Mike] Well if I
know that spider,
it's not a virgin bloody Mary!
- [Tom] Whee!
- [Crow] We still on of the
Richard Feinmen lecture?
- You look like you
could use a drink.
- [Tom] And a shower and a job.
- I found another body.
- [Mike] Good, yours is
getting pretty gross.
- Another cow?
- No, a human body.
- [Crow] It was walking along
the street and I killed it.
- A person?
- [Tom] Dutch will only
give me $0.39 a pound.
- But it was chewed up
worse than them cow.
- [Mike] Funny, I used
to like things like that.
- We need to call the sheriff.
- Are you out of your mind?
Now I buried that body,
and I hid the motorcycle,
no one will ever know.
- You're crazy!
- We can't let that sheriff
come nosing around here!
What if he finds the diamonds?
And all that grass
we're growing?
- [Tom] Wands are
illegal in Wisconsin?
- Well you sound like
you've been smoking
the stuff yourself.
- [Crow] Oh, my
bloody Mary has legs!
- [Mike] Charlotte's doing
bachelor parties now!
- [Crow] Wow, the
family on Tobacco Road
had a nicer farm than this.
- [Mike] Hey pal, you
got any curds and whey?
- [Tom] He's doing kind
of a grunge Amish look.
- [Crow] My assignment,
take out the greasy hick
with extreme prejudice.
- [Mike] I'm proud
to be a crap farmer.
- [Tom] Please sir, you're
standing on my wife.
- [Crow] Shine, mister?
(bird squawks)
- Why is he cawing?
- [Tom] I attempted the north
face of Mount Cheesehead.
- [Crow] Sheesh,
Mr. Touchy wigs out.
Hoo, hah, missed me!
- That creepeth upon the Earth
shall be an abomination.
- [Tom] Gotta nip it in the bud!
- [Preacher] Only the pure
of heart shall be spared.
- [Crow] Oh, spider's
barbecue got outta control.
- Ah, it's you.
- Don Juan DeStinko.
- I told ya I could
come again tonight.
- No!
- How'd you swing it, honey?
- Well I told the lush
that I hadda come
in and see my cousin
about some hot rocks.
(audience laughs)
- [Crow] Come on in,
let's do your taxes.
(Tom imitates a banjo)
- [Mike] That's a cute
room, and a whisky bottle,
just the right touch.
- [Crow] Isn't this
Annette Benning's bedroom
from InStyle magazine?
- [Tom] She ran out of
liquor so she's drinking
her Jean Netay.
- [Mike] No, that's the bed.
- [Crow] The Martha
Stewart we never see.
Well I'll hang
this up over there.
- [Mike] The spider's
using all eight eyes
now, I can tell you that.
♪ I enjoy being a victim
- [Mike] Invade!
- [Crow] Guys, guys?
♪ I feel shakey
♪ Oh so trembly, I've had whisky
♪ And vodka and gin
- [Tom] House is decorated
with the special Jim Varney
signature collection.
- [Crow] You and I are
very alike, join me!
- [Tom] This invasion
is awfully sluggish.
- [Mike] It's more like
a minor spider unrest.
- [Crow] Maybe if I left
him little love notes,
throw pork rinds on the bed.
- [Mike] I'm seeing two beds!
Oh, there are.
- [Crow] Japanese tea ceremony
taking place next store.
- [Tom] Tonight the bottle
came through in a big way!
- [Mike] What was I doing?
I wasn't drinking
there for a second.
- [Tom] Are we panning
down to her ab roller?
What the Hell's going on?
- [Crow] Bill
Rebane's trademark,
a shot of crumpled underpants.
- [Tom] What's that?
If you insist, I'll
have a drink, thanks.
- [Mike] Does the Fonz
usually sleep here
with his head against the wall?
- [Crow] Well I'm
feeling better,
at least I'm not
seeing spiders tonight.
- [Tom] Well, gotta get up
early to start drinking.
- [Crow] I need a
new pillow, and bed.
And a house, husband, life.
- [Tom] Torah, Torah, Torah!
- [Mike] Spider cut it
out honey, I'm tired.
- [Crow] Every night his
legs are all over me.
Securing butt, over.
- [Tom] I wish they
hadn't let us down
the giant spider path if
they couldn't deliver one.
- [Mike] I think they were
saying that a giant spider
would be nice, but
as an alternative,
please consider
our little movie.
- [Crow] Ah, music
budget ran out.
- [Mike] We're your
dirty socks, wash us!
- [Tom] Giant Puppet Invasion.
(Ev screams)
- [Mike] Yeah I know lady,
it's not my web honest, I'm
caught in this thing too.
- [Crow] Tonight on a
very special Waltons,
Mary Ellen runs around
in her underwear.
- [Mike] Mr. Lincoln,
Mr. Lincoln, Abe!
- [Crow] Okay let's see,
it's darker in here,
danker, no there won't be
any spiders in here, no siree.
(Ev screams)
- [Tom] My novelty throw pillow!
- [Mike] I'm a woosal,
and my name is peanut.
- [Crow] It's
morning in America,
the back braces are
a little sturdier.
- [Tom] And morning gin
tastes a little smoother.
- Hey, you forgot something.
- No, I got it on!
- Your heart drugs.
- Oh thank you.
I always give you a big tip.
- [Mike] Here's your naval lint.
- Thank you darling.
- [Tom] So this is
how Heidi turned out.
(bright synth music)
Back braces steamed and
cleaned, here it is!
- [Mike] My old boss, Mr. Gower!
- Cousin Dan!
- Cousin Eddie.
- Ah, what brings you to town?
Hey, how's that
hot little tomato
you're raising out there, huh?
- [Tom] Does he raise tomatoes?
- Terry's way overripe
for picking now!
- [Tom] I didn't know
he raised tomatoes.
- Oh, Terry's turning bad,
I can't control her anymore.
- Ah well, she needs a
gentle hand, like mine.
(audience groans)
- Here I got something
I wanna show ya.
What is that?
- That, that's a geode.
It's not from around here.
- [Crow] So let's beat it up!
- You musta found that
down south some place.
- Take a look at these,
just how good are
these diamonds here?
- [Tom] Are they
worth two months
of my welfare checks?
- [Mike] The diamond
anniversary ring,
tell you'd marry her
right out of high school
all over again.
- [Tom] Just seeing an old
fingernail with dirt under it,
oh wait that's mind (chuckles).
- [Crow] So seen Leatherface
around here lately?
- Well, just between you and me.
- Yeah, yeah?
(Eddie spits)
(audience groans)
- [Tom] Sir, you offend me!
- They're industrial quality,
and the carbon content
isn't nearly as high
as a real diamond.
No ring diamond.
- [Mike] Charles
Manson, jeweler.
- Well how much are they worth?
- Well, let's just say
if you had a bucket
full of these, barrel
full of these--
- [Tom] You'd be
a fat Cheesehead
with a barrel full of these.
- You might be rich.
Where'd you find these?
- Let's just say they
fell out of the sky!
- [Crow] Well met my friend,
this battle of wits is over!
♪ Ou, what a lucky man he was
- What's going on now?
- [Jenny] Those
satellite reports
you asked Paul Ryder to send.
- [Mike] Goody, back to the
really unappealing characters.
- [Tom] Lemme see
that, "Dear Chunkhead."
Well that's not nice!
- Latitude 45 degrees,
21 minutes west.
Correction north,
latitude 88 degrees,
42 minutes west, that's more
than a couple of square miles1
- I know.
- Well can't we pinpoint
it closer than that?
- Not from Telcom.
I'm afraid you're gonna
have to use a helicopter.
- [Mike] (laughs)
Let's have some tea.
- Tea!
- Okay.
- [Tom] There must
be an easier way
to find the angler's body.
- Gimme Paul Ryder please.
- [Crow] Paul Reiser,
this is a horror movie!
(dog barks)
- [Mike] Dead woods lolita.
- Well where the hell is Ev?
- [Terry] I don't know.
- [Tom] Ah, she's putting out
birth control pills for winter.
- [Mike] Oh Oscar, Oscar, Oscar.
- [Crow] Why is it so
neat and clean in here?
- [Tom] You didn't even try
to make it look like
a real police car!
- [Mike] Real stories of
the fake highway patrol.
- [Crow] Always let your
car settle for a minute.
- [Tom] The new Alan
Hale action figure,
he sits down, he snacks,
he sits down again,
he farts, he drives, he
comes with his own lunch!
- [Mike] Action Alan Hale
and Action Alan Hale's
gut sold separately.
- [Sheriff] Hello?
- [Crow] Walking Tall Three,
the high cholesterol years!
- Hi sheriff!
- Hi Terry!
Is Dan to home?
- [Mike] Well he's at home.
- Dan?
- [Crow] I suppose
you're wondering
what's eating Gilbert Grape.
- [Mike] Hey looking
for a new Gilligan,
you interested?
- Hi Dan.
I'm checking out a
missing person's report.
Mrs. Cooper asked me
to find her husband
and his motorcycle.
Now she says, "He
goes by here a lot
"and he's been missing
for a day and a half."
have you seen a
motorcycle around here?
- No.
- Well that closes the case.
- [Mike] And the
invasion's been crushed.
- Terry, you and dave seen
or heard a motorcycle?
How about Ev?
- Drunk as skunk?
- Where is she?
- Skunk.
- I don't know,
and I don't care.
- Well if either of you two
see or remember anything,
gimme a jingle, will you?
- [Tom] Good people,
salt of the earth!
- [Sheriff] Boy, that chopper
makes nearly as much noise
as that preacher man (laughs).
- [Mike] That must
be the chopper
to give him a lift
back to his car.
- [Tom] There's a
white trash spill
out on old possum junction.
- [Mike] Hello woman
in white pantsuit,
can you read me, over.
- [Pilot] I've located
a radioactive source.
Extremely high intensity.
- [Mike] And chocolately.
- Can you pinpoint?
- [Pilot] I'm over country road
and Copper Lake.
- That's near the Kester place.
- [Crow] Shut up, punk.
- What does it look like?
- [Pilot] (mumbles).
- [Tom] The pilot is
Charlie Brown's teacher.
- [Pilot] Do you read me?
(mumbles)
(audience mumbles)
I mean it's blurred and twisted.
- Get a picture of it.
- Get some wallet-sized.
- Get a picture of it
and rush it to the lab.
- [Pilot] Okay, will do.
- [Crow] Another
family vacation ruined.
- [Mike] It's a pretty
good drawing of the spider,
but I think they
only have eight legs.
- [Jenny] It fits, it's
space warp alright.
This must be the only
energy photgram of its kind.
- Well what's a space warp?
- [Mike] We made it up.
- Dave a space warp is
a gravitational pull
so intense that it makes
a Black Hole in space.
- [Tom] Like Linda Hunt!
- There's only one
thing I know of
that could cause
a warp like this.
- A miniature Black Hole.
- Could it happen?
- [Crow] Could the
movie get any worse?
- There's a billion Black Holes
in our galaxy, it's a wonder
it hasn't happened before.
- [Tom] It's about
time they got it going.
- Well Dr. Vance, Dr. Langer,
I've got to be going, thank you.
- [Vance] Bye Dave.
- [Crow] Well onto
our next guest now.
- [Vance] Well everything fits,
Einstein's general theory--
- [Mike] Goodbye Dave.
- If a dead star
collapsed all its masses.
- [Tom] A whole
bunch of its masses.
- The star would gradually
shrink to a point.
- [Vance] And disappear
into another universe.
- Right, a parallel universe
with a door back and forth.
- That sucks everything up.
- And throws everything out.
- [Crow] Like the sheriff.
- This maybe our problem.
Where is this--
- The metal open door.
- Kester farm?
- Oh it's...
It's somewhere in the
Harrison Hills area.
- [Tom] Paul and I brought
his operatives out there
for a picnic once.
- [Mike] Johnny Crappleseed.
- [Mike] Paul Infected Bunyon.
- [Tom] Old
MacDonald had a cyst.
- [Mike] Poor guy,
nobody came out
to the groundbreaking
for his new outhouse.
- [Crow] A
subterranean elephant.
♪ Way out here,
they've got a name
♪ For stinky, hairy white guys
- [Mike] I always
thought Mennonites
had more dignity.
- [Tom] Mike, if I
should slip into a coma
during this movie,
please please do not take
any extraordinary measures
to revive me, thank you.
- [Mike] Okay.
- [Crow] This guy
and Junior Samples
were in greater tuna together.
Hello, hello.
- [Tom] Why don't you watch it,
you dumb old spider you.
- If it had not been the Lord
who is on our side, then
they had (mumbles) up quick.
- [Crow] I'm drooling,
I know, I'm sorry.
- [Preacher] Hallelujah!
- [Congregation] Hallelujah!
- Hallelujah!
- It doesn't matter
if the spider ate
him with his butt.
- [Mike] I think it seems
suitable for this guy.
- [Crow] Can you
imagine how many interns
it took to pull that
guy up into the spider.
- Can I get off early tonight?
- Not before nine, why?
- I have an aunt coming
in from Vulvasota.
- Well if it's the same aunt
as last night, tell
her she left a hickey
on your neck!
- [Mike] My aunt
is KD Lang, okay?
- Dutch, what are we gonna
do about those damn spiders?
- We'll try to get the preacher
to exercise them.
- They're getting
enough exercise already!
- [Mike] The Dutch
and Helga show!
- Oh boy!
- [Crow] Now you can see
why Frank Llyod Wright
wanted to live in Wisconsin.
- [Tom] Here gimme that,
think I'm gonna
need all of that.
- [Mike] Hey, you wanna make
some crop circles
while we're here?
(bright synth music)
♪ Helter Skelter
- [Crow] Okay I'm in the seat,
Larry's on the wheel,
press the gas down!
- [Mike] Scatter, incoming butt!
♪ Have you seen
the little piggies
- [Mike] There goes the
town's diamond broker.
- [Tom] Ah what's the matter?
I said I'd give you gas money!
- [Mike] Ah, see what happens
when you don't check
your blind spot?
- [Tom] Oh no, a spider
a size of a Buick
is attacking his Buick, I
distinctly heard him say.
Wouldn't you know he's
outta wiper fluid.
- [Mike] Please sir, just
show me your registration.
- [Tom] Who do we bequeath
his Wet Willy albums to?
- [Crow] I hate it when a movie
kills off a beloved character.
This is great though!
- [Mike] Can't wait to
tell my friends about this,
oh wait, I'm a
friendless drifter.
- [Tom] Like he's resist
anything near his pants.
(man screams)
- Packers, woo!
Go Packers!
- [Crow] Honey, I'm home!
- [Tom] Honey, Packers
won the Super Bowl.
- Packers!
- Woo, Packers!
- [Mike] I'm starting to wish
the South would rise again
and crush the North.
(car horn blares)
- [Crow] Uh-oh, his hair
started a grease fire.
- [Mike] Y'know guys, I
know this makes it all
look pretty bad, but there
are a lot of good things
that come from Wisconsin,
like I don't know, fireworks,
and cheese, and fireworks.
- [Tom] Does Captain Stubbing
know you dress like that, Vicky?
- [Crow] He's been kicking
on the side of his
geode for hours.
- [Mike] I'm up, I'm
up, I'm ready, okay.
- [Tom] Bedroom's secure,
moving on to panty drawer!
(Terry screams)
- [Crow] I'm used to rats
and roaches, but this?
(Terry screams)
- [Mike] I said no starch!
- [Tom] Packers won
the Super Bowl, yay!
- [All] Woo!
- Billy Kester's
car just blew up.
- He's dead?
- Yup, he sure is,
deader than a doornail.
Y'know Dave, a lot
of strange things
are happening around here.
- Yeah I know, Dutch.
Can I use your phone?
- Sure, use my private
one in the back.
- Thanks Dutch.
- Okay.
- [Crow] So that's Dutch.
- [Jenny] This
should be the area.
- [Mike] For what I'm not sure.
- [Tom] This guy blows up
his neck waddles
to attract women.
- [Crow] Oh Phil, I'm
only wearing one pantsuit.
- [Vance] No count here.
- [Jrnny] Well there
has to be something!
- [Vance] Well it's
the normal count,
nothing dangerous.
- Guess their phone's dead.
- [Mike] Didn't we
just do this scene?
- [Tom] De ja vu.
- Listen, I think I'm
gonna go on out there.
- Okay.
- Man he's something,
when I was a kid I
never went on out there.
- [Crow] I wish I
could express my love
more openly and
freely to my wife.
(door slams)
- [Tom] One of this year's most
innovative new chefs, Dutch.
- Bob, Carl, Jack, Peter?
- [Crow] Wanna dance?
- Listen!
(woman screams)
- [Mike] At least she'll
be wrapped in something.
- [Tom] Bill Rebane,
movie maker and feminist.
- [Crow] Snuffaluffagus, no!
- [Mike] And just when things
were really looking up for her.
- [Tom] I put on too
much Indian earth, oh!
- [Crow] Just looking
for a clean glass here.
- [Tom] This actually
perks the place up.
- [Crow] Any comments
from you local shrubbery?
- [Tom] Y'know what
might help this scene
is if they were in
bikini underpants
and a halter top.
- Yeah.
- I don't know.
Well ma'am, we have
the demolition permit
right here, I'm sure
this is the right place.
- Vance?
- Yeah?
- [Jenny] What was that?
- [Tom] It was commerce,
tourism and industry
coming together in
beautiful Wisconsin.
- [Vance] I didn't
hear anything.
- [Crow] I married
a land surveyor.
- [Tom] Oh, here comes
a Duke of Hazard.
- [Mike] It's everyone I
went to high school with.
- [Crow] I'm sure.
Any of you ladybugs have any
comments about the spider?
- [Tom] He shot Dan!
- [Mike] Oh no,
it's spider season
and we didn't wear orange!
- That sounds like a
high powered rifle!
- This isn't hunting season.
- [Vance] C'mon,
let's get out of here.
- [Mike] No one hunts out
of season in Wisconsin.
(rifle fires)
- [Tom] He thought I was dead.
- [Crow] This is one of those
prestigious gated communities.
(Tom imitates an engine)
- [Crow] Jim's Girl salvage.
- [Tom] Ah, greasy girls
carrying unconscious girls,
comfortable 2:00 pm beer
buzz, ya home sick yet Mike?
- [Mike] (laughs)
That's very funny.
His Hagar pants have a waistband
with repressed memories.
- [Tom] Please, consider my
legs when cleaning your pipe.
(audience laughs)
- [Crow] There goes the last
shred of dignity, folks.
- [Mike] Barbara
Hale and Doughy Guy
in The Defiant Ones.
Thrill as he
doesn't reduce speed
when approaching
Elroy, Danbury, Toma!
- [Jenny] Oh my God!
- [Crow] You rolled on me!
(monster shrieks)
- [Mike] When this is over,
they deserve a lotta Liney's,
a deep-fried cheese curds,
and some funnel cakes.
- [Tom] Nigel Tufnel's
playing a guitar solo.
- [Crow] We've got
to get to PetSmart
to buy a box of enormous flies!
- [Tom] This can't be Wisconsin,
there's no billboards for
Tommy Bartlett's water show.
- [Mike] Room service.
- [Tom] What should
I be doing back here?
Oh sorry, I'm not
supposed to, bye.
- [Crow] What if they
ran into another patient?
They'd have to back
all the way up.
- [Mike] The shroud of Debbie.
- [Tom] With this
Muscilage, I thee wed.
- Here Doctor.
- Thank you.
- All Hell has broken loose,
it's gonna be hard to
keep the lid on now.
- Yeah we know all
about it, sheriff.
- My stomach is
doing flip flops,
we just brought back what
was left of Joe Cooper.
- [Crow] He's the urpy sheriff
with the delicate constitution.
- Sheriff, if your
stomach can handle it.
- [Mike] I'd like to show
you my vasectomy scar.
- We've got a 50 foot spider
out there on the loose.
- 50 foot spider?
- Actually it's a
furry dune buggy.
- You mean that's
what got Joe Cooper?
- Looks like our Black Hole
has turned into an
open doorway from hell.
- [Crow] Sorry, I mean
open doorway from heck.
- And we're gonna have to
find a way to close it.
- God knows how many
monsters may come through.
- And how many have
already come through.
- [Mike] We better
put up snow fences.
- Doctor please, what
are these gizmos?
I found them near the corpse.
- [Tom] They're
petrified tribbles!
- You found 'em where?
- Near the corpse.
- [Crow] That's that
new club downtown.
- Sheriff do you
mind if we take these
and run some tests on 'em?
- No please do.
- Oh thank you, do you have
a flare gun we could use?
- Yes, you could pick one
up with the desk sergeant,
he's got a couple
of flares out there.
- Thank you.
- Thank you sheriff.
- [Mike] Thank you
fellow has been.
- [Vance] We'll keep in touch.
- Thank you.
- Boy, problems are hard.
(phone rings)
- [Crow] Pork Vacuum,
I mean Sheriff?
- Hello?
Yes, this is the sheriff.
(siren blares)
- [Mike] Sorry, I can
only speak in siren.
- Oh Davey--
- I thought you were lunch.
- I didn't recognize your
voice, yes what is it?
- [Mike] Little buddy,
trouble, lagoon?
- Is Terry alright?
- [Crow] Action phone scene.
- Well have Doc Oliphant
check her, will you?
- [Tom] And have him send
over a hospital meal.
- And kep me filled in
on everything, please.
Thanks Davey.
- [Mike] Gee Davey, keep
me filled in everything.
- 50 foot spider?
- Vance?
Sorry to take so
long, but the lab
said it will take
a full two hours
to get a report on these.
The only thing they said
was they'd never seen
anything like them.
- [Crow] Early breast implants.
- Should I crack 'em open?
- [Tom] Sure, I'm drunk.
- We don't have time for that!
First things first,
we gotta find some way
to get out there and
kill that monster.
- Oh how are you gonna
kill a monster like that?
An alien energy pattern?
We haven't even
found the impact area
of the Black Hole.
- And that's undoubtedly where
the spider's coming from.
- Right, the energy pattern
has to feed off the
gravitational field
of the Black Hole.
- [Mike] I can't believe
I let you roll on me.
- Vance, could we
soak up the energy?
- We could feed it
so much extra mass,
we could choke it.
- We could shower
it with neutrons.
- [Crow] Or we can
do the Neutron Dance!
- Neutron initiated.
- [Tom] Admit it, you felt
something when I rolled on ya.
- It just might work.
(doors slam)
- Oh I'm telling you guys,
this whole thing
is freaking me out!
I mean the idea of each
of being replicated,
and having to, oh hi Servo,
I was just telling
these guys (screams)!
You get out of here Mister!
You're a fake, a fake!
- But I am Tom Servo
of fine high quality.
- Wow, I think I like
that Servo better.
- Crow!
- Crow.
- Now hold on here, now we
gotta get to the bottom of this.
Now how do I know
you're the real Servo?
- Why Mike, don't you remember
when we did that fun thing
together that was so fun
that one time?
- (laughs) Oh yeah,
that was fun, wasn't it?
- Wait a minute Mike,
you and I did a fun
together once too, right?
- No, I don't remember that.
- Hang on, hang on,
there's a real easy
to figure this out.
I'll ask a question that only
the real Servo would know!
Okay, what condiment did
I pour into your sneakers
only two weeks ago?
- Oh, um, uh--
- Was it ketchup?
- Yes!
- Damn!
You are me, gee I
guess I am a fraud.
- Now hold on, hold on,
let's go two out of three.
Okay, what's your
confirmation name?
(Tom whispers to fake Tom)
- Now Mike, we're gonna say
that we don't have
a confirmation name.
- Well you're right
actually, okay.
Well let's try one more though.
What do you have in your
underwear collection?
- Oh please, you would have
to be a total pathetic loser
of the lowest quality to
have an underwear collection.
- (laughs) 342 pairs of
cotton boxers, no duplicates,
78 pairs of silk boxers,
702 pairs of high-cut briefs,
55 pairs of low-cut briefs,
seven banana warmers,
one pair of Home of
the Whopper brief,
one pair of Joe Nameth netted
slingshot brief prototypes!
(Fake Tom screams)
- Loser, loser I won, woo-hoo!
- Frankly I don't know
why we need any
Servo at all, Mike.
- Man knows his underwear,
we'll be right back.
- Woo, woo, woo, woo.
- Shh!
(bright synth music)
- What's up?
- I want you to fly me--
- [Crow] Are you supposed
to be able to hear this?
- Right away.
- That's a pretty stiff order.
- [Mike] See city managers
deal with traffic issues.
- Tell him to load it
with a 600 gram charge
and set the pattern
at 360 degrees.
- [Man] My chopper will
pick it up at the airport.
- Alright, if it doesn't work,
then old buddy we got
company for dinner.
Three hours, bye.
- Three hour tour.
- Well it sounds
like just the ticket.
Tell me, how does one
of those gizmos work?
- [Mike] Sandwiches
dipped in batter
and then deep-fried?
What the--
- [Crow] Are we supposed to
know who he's talking to?
I mean.
- [Mike] Hello?
Movie?
- Movie?
- Yoo-hoo, movie!
- Over here!
(Tom whistles)
- Right here!
- Alright, thanks Vance.
- [Mike] These are
the famous scenes
that Alan Hale improvised.
- [Crow] Alan Hale literally
phoned in his role.
- I'll tell you, you know
what happened to the Kesters.
(funk jazz music)
Now the spider's nest is
somewhere on the Kester's ranch,
you all have guns,
when we leave here,
we're gonna pick up
all the relatives,
friends, neighbors,
anybody we can find,
and we're gonna go
out to Kester's farm
and we're gonna
destroy that spider,
so c'mon, let's go!
- [Tom] Put down
those pull tabs men,
we have work to do!
(men scream)
- [Crow] R Crumb
is leading them.
- [Mike] For Grandma Smreacar!
- [Vance] Hey fellas
wait a minute!
- [Tom] Let's just
kill each other.
- [Vance] Now like
I said inside,
I want each of you to go
in a different direction.
I want you to get your
friends, relatives,
anybody you can.
- [Crow] What if my friends
don't have relatives?
(multiple people speak at once)
- [Sheriff] Dutch,
what's going on?
Alright, everybody--
- Packers!
(audience woos)
- You're a trouble maker,
I'm trying to tell
you to knock it off,
now everybody go home--
- We're not gonna give in--
- Knock it off!
- Oh you knock it off!
Alright let's go, c'mon!
- [Mike] Wait a
minute, we can't hunt,
we're not drunk enough yet.
- [All] Packers, woo!
- [Mike] Please, if
you'll all just go back
to your drinking.
- [Sheriff] Alright,
everybody just--
- [Crow] Wang Chung tonight!
- [Tom] That's Old Milwaukee
coming out of there.
- [Mike] Just swing
us 'til we die.
- [Crow] Ride the vomit rainbow!
Twirling fans of technoconion
splayed across the sky!
- [Tom] Hopefully we'll
work up enough speed
to launch us into Minnesota
instead of real life!
- [Mike] It's been an
hour, please let us down.
- [Crow] You know carnies
are actually the most respected
citizens in this town.
- [Tom] Honk, honk, vroom!
- [Mike] It's Suicide
Days in New Richmond.
- [Crow] I wanna go
pet the wounded goat!
- [Mike] You sure this is as
fast as this thing can go?
- [Tom] Back!
- [Crow] It's
Milling Around Days.
- [Tom] Hawaiian's club
medium rare chicken booth!
- [Crow] Free
range and beer fed.
- [Mike] Basted with
sun-brewed mayonnaise.
- [Tom] The Spare
Days is fun this year!
- [Crow] This is where you'd
find a crocheted beer can hat.
- [Tom] How sweet it is!
- [Mike] And the
score is 78 to five
in the bottom of
the third inning.
- Packers won the Super Bowl!
- Packers, woo!
- [Tom] Previously owned
cheese curds are on sale.
- [Crow] Ou he stood up,
he's gotta get
hazard pay for this.
- [Mike] I had a hot
dog in here once.
(phone rings)
- [Tom] He could do a one man
show playing Queen Victoria.
- Hello?
Yeah this is the sheriff.
- [Crow] You discovered
a new kind of meat?
- What?
- [Mike] Pork gravy from a can?
- In Gleason?
- [Tom] Does Jackie mind?
- Are you sure they're
headed this way?
- [Crow] Did they
bring a dish to pass?
- Okay.
- [Mike] It's a cheese
fueled mob frenzy.
- [Tom] Welcome to
Beer Hall Putsch Days.
- [Crow] Oh, John Malkovitch!
- Hello Operator?
- Where's Gleason?
- Get me the National Guard
headquarters in Madison.
(tires squeal)
- [Tom] When
snowmobilers drive cars!
(explosion)
- [Crow] You can't really
blame a spider for that.
- [Mike] Too late, insurgents
overthrew the Barabool regime.
- [Crow] Patrick?
- [Tom] There's them organs,
we didn't put 'em on
ice, hope that's okay.
- [Mike] Here take
some zucchini,
we had so much this year.
- [Crow] By the way this is
Wisconsin's National Guard.
- [Tom] Audiences
won't soon forget,
when the thing we
didn't know what it was
was put in a helicopter
by the guy we didn't know.
(crickets chirp)
- [Crow] Are we dead, Mike?
- [Jenny] Once you seal off
the hole, what's gonna happen?
- [Crow] What's gonna happen?
(audience groans)
- There's gonna be an
army of those spiders
crawling around,
growing, and multiplying.
- [Mike] Rebane was filming
night to night here, was he?
- Yes.
- [Crow] It's Dr. Honey to you.
- [Tom] Oh no, it's a fish boil!
- [Mike] We don't need to put
our nuclear waste into casks.
- [Crow] "Dark, it's not dark."
Rebane declared.
- [Tom] Visuals for a
movie, who needs 'em!
- [Mike] And somewhere
in the world,
a helicopter exists.
- [Jenny] Lord knows
how many of those
things are around here.
- Just take it easy.
- Let's you and I
go up to dry land and
roll on each other.
- [Crow] When grandma's
go spelunking.
- [Mike] You're falling on me!
- Oh God, another one.
- [Jenny] Let's get out of here.
- [Tom] Let's go have a
nice dinner at the goblin.
- [Crow] Oh it's a, huh?
- [Mike] Robert MacNamera
escalates the war on Gleason.
- [Tom] Can we roll the
rest of the way to the car?
- [Crow] Emergency, I'm
winded and I'm very moist.
- Patch me through
to the sheriff.
- [Mike] Maybe if I kill myself
like Hemingway, people
will remember me fondly!
(phone rings)
- [Tom] Oh, that'll be my
shift down at Skippers!
- [Crow] Rebane and Hale,
like Scorcese and Deniro.
- Hello?
(Tom imitates a fart)
Yeah Vance.
- [Mike] I'm sitting.
- The spiders are
all over Gleason,
just a few miles away.
- [Crow] I'll drive
my 'Lark there.
- Yes, I've called for
the National Guard--
- But he's not in.
- The mobs are beginning
to gather and they're
getting on of hand!
- Look get somebody out here,
I just found another body
or what's left of one,
and for God's sake keep
that mob away from here!
- [Crow] It's more of a
moblet, kind of a light crowd.
- [Mike] Ah, the mob
demands whoopee John.
- [Tom] So they're really
giving over to mob mentality
to stand around and mingle.
- Packers!
- Woo!
- Packers.
- Packers?
- You know why we're all here.
- Yeah Packers!
- You've all got your
guns, you're all on it.
- [Mike] The Margarine
Riot of 1974.
- Free Bobby Seal!
- Free Mumbia!
- [Mike] Free beer!
- C'mon now, I want you to
get out of here, all of ya.
- [Tom] Toughing GED
standards, no fair!
- Boo!
- Woo!
- Packers!
- Packers.
- [Sheriff] I got
a man from NASA
and he knows what he's doing.
- Packers.
- Woo.
- [Man] We'll handle
it ourselves, c'mon!
- [Crow] US out of North
America, and Packers!
- [Mike] Woo, no more schools,
more hockey arenas.
- [Crow] More Packers!
- [Tom] Packers!
- We almost got
hit by the monster,
the crowd's getting out of hand,
I can't control 'em!
They're Hell bent on
destroying that beast.
- [Crow] We're Hell bent.
- Did you ever see
the movie Jaws?
Well it makes that shark
look like a goldfish!
- I know, I know.
- The better movie.
- Try to keep 'em there
as long as you can,
we're setting up
the lights around,
and the bomb's on it's way,
and try to keep
the spider there.
- [Sheriff] We can't do
anything with the spider,
bullets don't hurt it!
The only thing
I've got to stop it
here with is a traffic light!
- Sheriff, at least try.
- [Tom] There's baby
urp on his shoulder.
- [Crow] Okay forget it
spider, you win sorry!
Sorry, sorry.
- I'm down here all by myself.
Call the National Guard back,
tell them we need
some heavy equipment!
- Fur is murder!
- Anything!
- [Tom] Violence
erupted when Dave Dudley
canceled his
appearance in Gleason.
(monster shrieks)
- [Mike] I'm heading over
to Taco John's 'til
this blows over!
(bright synth music)
- [Crow] Just honk at it, honey.
(horn honks)
- Give my ham's waterfall sign
to my son.
- As the end
of the world begins.
Luke Chapter 21--
- (gasps) Dutch!
Oh Dutch.
- Too many Jello shots.
- [Mike] No more tainted
meat sandwiches, Dutch.
- Shall be in diverse places--
- Is there a verse
in the Bible that tells us
when the end of
this movie is near?
- [Preacher] And great signs
shall there be from Heaven!
- The spider is retreating,
heading out of town,
we've got a lot of
people hurt here!
- [Tom] Somehow this
will all tie back
to the yellow back brace.
- Packers.
- Packers?
- Spider's gone,
get out of here.
- [Mike] Uh Mr. Rebane, we
really can't see anything.
- [Tom] Look, just shut
up and keep shooting,
Mr. NYU Film Pants.
- [Jenny] You know that big
one is like a mother queen bee.
- [Vance] Yes, and
she's activated
all the spiders in
this whole area.
- [Jenny] You think the smaller
ones'll grow to be giants?
- [Vance] Well it could be,
unless that neutron
gadget works.
- I wish that
chopper'd get here!
- Here comes somebody now!
- [Crow] Why it's Barney!
- [Tom] You gotta
nip it the bud, Andy!
It's my emergency
shipment of Lucky Strikes.
- Vance!
- What?
- That big one, I just
saw it up on the highway.
It's cutting through the woods
and it's heading this direction.
- [Crow] These are
just the drunks,
they haven't even gotten
to the wounded yet.
- [Mike] It's a VW in chenille.
- [Tom] I understand
you can repair
these giant spiders yourself.
- Here comes the chopper now.
- [Tom] It's a vegetable
chopper though.
- Can you patch me through?
- Sure Vance.
- [Mike] Is this
gonna be another case
of a scientist
declaring martial law?
- [Crow] I wish John
Agar we're in it.
- Kane this is Vance,
Kane this is Vance,
use your spotlight as a target
and drop the gadget.
- No!
- [Kane] You want me land
and give you the trigger?
- Hell no!
- Sorry, just asking.
- Look, I'm gonna fire a flare
and you pull the trigger!.
- No!
- Okay.
- Follow us.
- She's dressed
like an Elvis impersonator.
- [Tom] If you see only
10,000 movies this year,
make sure this
isn't one of them.
- [Crow] Soon Hitler's
giant mechanical spiders
had pushed pass
the Magineaux line.
- Jenny?
- Yeah?
- I forgot the flares.
(Mike laughs)
- [Vance] They're
in the briefcase,
would you get 'em?
- I'll get them.
- [Tom] On the way to shoot
the flares, I forgot them.
- [Mike] A brilliant
plot device,
forgetting to do
a simple errand.
- [Vance] We've got company!
(spider shrieks)
- [Crow] These spiders
have lousy heaters though.
- We're gonna keep her out
on the black cove
until we make the drop.
- Okay, I'm gonna try.
- Good boy.
- [Tom] He looks like
Bigfoot in business casual.
- [Mike] Spider's gonna
have a heart attack
from eating so many Cheeseheads.
- [Crow] Jog walk out of danger!
- [Tom] Ah, this lawn line
is really cutting into me.
- [Mike] I just wanna get my
Pall Malls while I'm here.
(woman screams)
- [Crow] God I hate paperwork.
(Mike cries)
- [Tom] Hey spider, you have
a ball hitch, mine is busted.
(gun fires)
- I'm the twin brother
of Dutch, the man you murdered!
- [Mike] Remember,
I mate, then I kill.
- [Tom] I'm gonna squash
your shoe under me.
- [Crow] Bad spider, sit bad!
- [Tom] This man is a
brave, brave character
we've never seen before.
- [Mike] Normally I
stuff people in my butt,
but in your case I'll let
you come in the front way.
- [Crow] Wow, another spider's
gonna have to come along
and give the guy a boost up.
- [Tom] Oh boy, he's carrying
him like a loaf of bread.
Oh, and he drops him
at the 10 yard line.
- [Mike] I injected a paralyzing
toxin into the sheriff,
but I did not inject
a paralyzing toxin
into the deputy.
- [Crow] Oh no, he bit right
into the guy's fountain pen.
- [Tom] And yet, Bill
Rebane escapes unharmed.
- How big is it?
- It's as big as a house!
- [Mike] Oh crap, my shoe.
- [Jenny] Vance, Vance!
- What happened?
- Spider's came out
of the briefcase--
(Crow cries)
- Gimme this, c'mon!
(multiple people speak at once)
Everybody get out of there!
Hurry up, c'mon!
- [Tom] Quit picking tobacco,
we're making a movie here
you damn migrant workers.
- Get down!
- Get funky.
Ah, the firework.
- [Tom] And the blast
was felt yards away.
- [Mike] The first extremely
tentative atomic test
in Omagordon.
What?
- Alright.
- [Tom] I am Death,
destroyer of lawns.
- [Mike] Spider must
have been really wet.
- [Crow] But I came
with a knowledge
for a cheap, clean
alternative to fossil fuel.
- [Tom] Remember,
don't put your spider
in the microwave if you
wrap it with tin foil.
- [Crow] Mom, I need a bucket.
- [Tom] It came from
planet Grossout.
I ate too much ice cream!
- [Mike] Spider needs a Zantac.
- [Crow] Alan Hale
digests a kielbasa.
- [Tom] I guess
somebody tampered
in God's domain or something.
- Don't let it happen again!
- [Crow] Remember
don't buy margarine,
only creamery butter.
- [Preacher] Refuse
the children of Isreal
their right to excess,
the Heavens open up
and deludes the land
with flies, frogs,
lice, and locusts!
It happened before and
it will happen again.
- [Mike] And now we'll
pass the collection plate.
- [Tom] Guys I think we're deep
into film student
territory here.
- [Crow] And Andrea
Scharf begat Kevin Brodie
who begat Alan Rebane!
- [Tom] I think the problem
was there weren't enough
Rebanes in this movie.
- [Crow] The Brodie to Rebane
ratio is a little rich.
- [Mike] Buck Gillett,
what if Buck Gillett
were the best a man could get?
- [Crow] Y'know when Barbara
Hale won the Oscar for this,
she made a touching speech,
where she said in
effect, "Thanks!"
- [Tom] The filmmaker
gratefully acknowledges
the cooperation of the goblin,
the Chi Highlerman
brewing company,
the Doughboy incorporation,
Ford Hower toilet paper,
Plackman's mustard company,
the Bodines, the America
Dairy Association,
and the Wisonsin chapter
of Wisconsin Dairy Farmers,
and the violent films.
- [Crow] Oh like this film
had a worldwide release.
- [Tom] Dedicated to the memory
of Crazy Legs Elroy Hearsch.
- Go Packers.
(doors slam)
Pods everywhere, come
on, some on, bah!
Ah Crow, thank
goodness it's you,
I think it's just you and me,
I think we're the
only normal ones left.
(Crow shrieks)
Oh my God, Bobo we
have to do something!
Please tell me you're not a pod.
- Oh me?
No, everyone else is
down here, not me.
You wanna know why not me?
Because a monkey isn't
good enough, again!
Should we assimilate the monkey?
No, the monkey's got a red butt,
stupid monkey's got a red butt,
does the monkey want a banana?
It takes its toll, Mike.
- Would you please
forget about all of that?
Look the universe is in peril
and you have to save it,
and the way I figure it,
there's gotta be a mother
pod down there somewhere.
- Oh me save the galaxy?
Mike, I'm a stupid monkey,
I might as well admit it.
I do have a red butt,
let's face that.
Have you ever seen my butt?
Here, take a good
look at my butt.
- No no, Bobo listen to me.
Hold on a second.
See, see ball, see, go!
Listen to me, you've got
to find the mother pod
and destroy it, you can do it,
you are a magnificent
mountain gorilla!
You are Bobo, son of Coco!
- Yes, and heir to the
great lineage of Godo!
Bogo, and Timtim!
Now where's that mother pod?
(Bobo grunts)
- Yes.
- Mike, you okay?
- Mike are you alright?
- Yeah yeah, I'm
alright, how about you?
- Well we're okay too,
and they had us locked up!
- Yeah.
- Ah, ya big lug.
All I can say is (shrieks).
I was kidding!
- Well I guess we just
gotta get the dry husks
of our dupplegangers
out of here, huh?
Back to you Bobo.
- Ooga shaka, ooga
ooga ooga shaka,
ooga ooga ooga shaka.
Oh blood giver, I saved you!
I am so glad to see you!
- Bobo, get your paws off me!
Have you been drinking?
- No no, look see,
here's dead you,
and Observer,
here's dead pod you,
you see all the time we
were watching the movie,
you were a pod!
I saved you and
the whole galaxy,
aren't cha proud?
- You mean they
watched the movie
and I didn't get to watch
them watching the movie?
Bobo get rid of my body,
Brain Guy send them
the movie again.
- [All] Movie Sign, again!
(somber horn music)
(Man blows raspberry)